flylink.info 2016-12-21

# FlyLink Travel Privacy Policy

Except where otherwise required or permitted by law, FlyLink Travel will inform individuals of the purpose for the collection, use or disclosure of the individual’s personal information, prior to the collecting, using or disclosing that personal information.

FlyLink Travel collects information from clients and potential clients through various means including application forms, web-form registrations, marketing campaign, purchase/sale agreements and survey responses. The type of information collected will vary depending on the means through which an individual submits his/her personal information. The type of information collected may include an individual’s name, residential address, email address, home phone number, age group, preferences, credit information and specific comments.

FlyLink Travel uses information collected from clients and potential clients to provide services or products, in respond to the requests for information or the purchase of FlyLink Travel’s products & services; for mailing contacts for FlyLink Travel publications, marketing materials, special events or other marketing activity and for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected. FlyLink Travel also uses personal information from purchasers for accounting and transactional completion purposes.

FlyLink Travel may disclose personal information to legal, financial and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of or its business or operations.

Requirement for consent to the collection, use or disclosure of personal information vary depending on circumstances and on the type of personal information that is intended to be collected, used or disclosed. In determining whether consent is required and, if so, which form of consent is appropriate, FlyLink Travel will take into account both the sensitivity of the personal information at issue and the purposes for which FlyLink Travel will use the information.

Consent may be express, implied through the use of opt-out consent where applicable or deemed. On giving reasonable written notice to FlyLink Travel, an individual may withdraw consent to the collections, use or disclosure of his or her personal information. Upon receipt of this withdrawal, FlyLink Travel will notify the individual of the likely consequences of withdrawing their consent. Except where otherwise required or permitted by law, FlyLink Travel will then cease collecting, using or disclosing the individual’s personal information.
